[{"success": true, "timeout": false, "failed_images": [], "failed_audio": [], "failed_video": [], "trial_type": "preload", "trial_index": 0, "time_elapsed": 302, "internal_node_id": "0.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 94370, "stimulus": ["<p> Welcome! </p> <p> We are conducting an experiment about how people evaluate intuitive physics situations when asked a question in plain english. Your answers will be used to inform computer science and cognitive science research.</p><p> This experiment should take no more than <strong>10 minutes</strong></p> <p> We take your time seriously! The email for the main experimenter is <strong>juliush@mit.edu</strong>. </br></br> Please write this down now, and email us with the subject line <i>Human experiment for intuitive physics</i> if you have problems submitting this task, or if it takes much more time than expected. </p><p>  Press any key to begin. </p>"], "response": " ", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 1, "time_elapsed": 94673, "internal_node_id": "0.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 56307, "stimulus": ["<p>In this experiment, you will be presented with a series of images containing <strong>stacks of blocks and some simple questions.</strong></p><p>The block are stacked on a grey platform in a configuration which may or may not be stable.</p><p>In each situation, you will be asked to imagine what will occur after a sufficiently large amount of time has passed and gravity has finished acting on the stacks of blocks.", "<p>Your task will be to think about how these blocks will fall and their position <strong>after they have finished falling</strong>. Note that sometimes, you may be presented with a stable stack where no blocks will fall.<p>You will enter your answer for each question by clicking a rating on a <strong>7-point multiple choice scale</strong> ranging from <strong>1 (definitely no)</strong> to <strong>7 (definitely yes)</strong>.", "<p>You will see descriptions of <strong>24  different scenarios</strong> in total.</p><p> When you are ready, please click any key to complete a quick comprehension check, before moving on to the experiment. </p>"], "response": " ", "trial_type": "html-keyboard-response", "trial_index": 2, "time_elapsed": 150981, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 15477, "response": {"Q0": "Look at images containing blocks and answer questions about what will happen in the image after gravity has acted on the blocks.", "Q1": "By selecting an option from a multiple choice scale."}, "question_order": [0, 1], "trial_type": "survey-multi-choice", "trial_index": 3, "time_elapsed": 166461, "internal_node_id": "0.0-2.0-1.0"}, {"rt": 18336, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "42", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 4, "time_elapsed": 184799, "internal_node_id": "0.0-3.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7349, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "13", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 5, "time_elapsed": 192149, "internal_node_id": "0.0-4.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 11717, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "46", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 6, "time_elapsed": 203867, "internal_node_id": "0.0-5.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 29732, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "14", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 7, "time_elapsed": 233600, "internal_node_id": "0.0-6.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 71917, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "47", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 8, "time_elapsed": 305523, "internal_node_id": "0.0-7.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 91118, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "4", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "26", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 9, "time_elapsed": 396646, "internal_node_id": "0.0-8.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 35477, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "8", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 10, "time_elapsed": 432129, "internal_node_id": "0.0-9.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9660, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will most of the blocks have stayed on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "45", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 11, "time_elapsed": 441795, "internal_node_id": "0.0-10.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 20619, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "41", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 12, "time_elapsed": 462421, "internal_node_id": "0.0-11.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6856, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "10", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 13, "time_elapsed": 469283, "internal_node_id": "0.0-12.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 9237, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "40", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 14, "time_elapsed": 478527, "internal_node_id": "0.0-13.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 22624, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "1", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "12", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 15, "time_elapsed": 501156, "internal_node_id": "0.0-14.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 18428, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "19", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 16, "time_elapsed": 519590, "internal_node_id": "0.0-15.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 6406, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "36", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 17, "time_elapsed": 526002, "internal_node_id": "0.0-16.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 23969, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "5", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 18, "time_elapsed": 549975, "internal_node_id": "0.0-17.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 24031, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "16", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 19, "time_elapsed": 574013, "internal_node_id": "0.0-18.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7031, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "6", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "37", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 20, "time_elapsed": 581049, "internal_node_id": "0.0-19.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 21291, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "2", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 21, "time_elapsed": 602347, "internal_node_id": "0.0-20.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7937, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be more red blocks to the left of the platform than purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "7", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "44", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 22, "time_elapsed": 610290, "internal_node_id": "0.0-21.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 13235, "response": {"Q0": 1}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "2", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "18", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 23, "time_elapsed": 623531, "internal_node_id": "0.0-22.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7889, "response": {"Q0": 6}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the majority of the large blocks be on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "3", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "24", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 24, "time_elapsed": 631426, "internal_node_id": "0.0-23.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 10924, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any red blocks remaining on the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "1", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 25, "time_elapsed": 642356, "internal_node_id": "0.0-24.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 5381, "response": {"Q0": 5}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will there be any purple blocks to the right of the platform?", "box_ensemble_index": "0", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "4", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 26, "time_elapsed": 647744, "internal_node_id": "0.0-25.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 7784, "response": {"Q0": 0}, "question_order": [0], "english_question": "After some time has passed, will the number of blocks on the platform be divisible by 3?", "box_ensemble_index": "5", "task": "answer_physical_image_questions", "task_id": "35", "trial_type": "survey-likert", "trial_index": 27, "time_elapsed": 655534, "internal_node_id": "0.0-26.0-0.0"}, {"rt": 27086, "response": {"Q0": "10", "Q1": "1", "Q2": "physics", "Q3": ""}, "trial_type": "survey-text", "trial_index": 28, "time_elapsed": 682639, "internal_node_id": "0.0-27.0"}]